（忆往昔）
克莱尔…你如果踏上我们走的路
You know, Claire, you go down this path, our path,
活不长的
it's not a long life.
我郑重发誓不会像傻瓜一样猎魔
I solemnly swear not to hunt like a dumbass.
克莱尔 干蠢事之前千万做好功课
Claire, do your homework before you do anything stupid, okay?
如果需要我们 我们随叫随到
And we're here if you need us, any time.
被纯种头四代子孙
"Werewolves that are turned up to four generations.
所转化的狼人相对温和 并且可以在
from pureblood are less feral and can transform.
任何时候变形
before, during, and after the lunar cycle"
狼人都很厉害
I mean, werewolves are badass.
长老要温家人
The old men want the Winchesters,
我就去争取迪恩了
so I made a play for Dean,
本来挺成功 结果你的行动出了岔子
and it was working until your operation went sideways.
我加入 你们在改变世界 我想加入进来
I'm in. You're changing the world, and I wanna be a part of it.
迪恩 多亏米克和他的人
Dean, because of Mick and his guys,
吸血鬼始祖死了
the Alpha Vampire is dead.
我还能说什么 我喜欢这样吗 不喜欢
What do you want me to say? Do I like it? No.
我信任他们吗 绝不
Do I trust them? Hell, no.
我们经常跟我们不信任的人合作
We work with people we don't trust all the time.
如果你想试试看 那好吧
So if you wanna give this a shot, then fine.
（如今）
（冰啤 红酒 外带）
（幸运獾酒吧 麦芽酒）
你说我撒谎 不是吧
"Are you calling me a liar? Seriously?"
没错 是的
Yeah. Seriously.
你被逮到了
You're so busted.
你逊毙了
You are beyond lame, you know that?
我们回去吧 求你
Let's just go back. Please?
我能让你进去
I'll get you in.
喝过莫斯科骡子吗
Ever had a Moscow Mule?
什么
A Moscow Mule?
你能不能 哪怕一次 有点你这年纪的样子
Will you just, for once, act your age?
你连自己的车都没有还好意思说
Says the guy who doesn't even have his own car.
别再缠着妈妈给我们买车了 好吗
Stop hounding Mom about buying us a car, all right?
她已经在尽力了
She's doing the best she can.
再过两年 我就走人
Two more years, I am so gone.
等等
Hold up!
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
嗯 那叫动物
Yeah. They're called animals.
- 我们回镇上吧 - 不 海登 我们走
- Let's just go back into town. - No, Hayden, we're going.
你是没看过恐怖片吗
Have you, like, never seen a horror movie?
两个孩子 阴暗小路
Two kids, dark road,
林子里发出恐怖的声响
creepy noise in the woods?
我们再走就…
We keep walking… and boom!
你真能闹
You are such a drama queen.
- 那里什么都没有 - 但我…
- All right, there's nothing there. - But I …
好吧 我证明给你看
No, fine. I'll prove it.
白痴
Sucker.
（亲爱的 就回来）
瞧
See?
我说的吧
Told you.
海登
Hayden!
海登 不
Hayden… No.
天呐 小海
Oh, my God. Hay.
救命
Help!
海登 海登 海登
Hayden, Hayden, Hayden, Hayden.
[邪恶力量 第12季第16集]
好吧 够了 我去车里等
All right, that's it. I'm waiting in the car.
- 迪恩 哥们 等等 - 不
- Dean, dude, wait a second. - No. You know what?
从这帮混蛋那儿接活儿是一码事
Getting jobs from these dicks is one thing,
但我可不想玩什么到岗报到这套
but I didn't sign up for this reporting for duty crap,
- 他们还迟到 - 抱歉迟到了
- especially when they're late. - Sorry I'm late.
我向总部的报告电话打了很久
My report to the home office ran long.
我们一直很忙…
We've had our hands full since…
还是别再多想了
Well, best not to dwell on that.
好压抑
That is some world-class repression.
你还真是英国人
You are British.
我们更喜欢称之为镇定自若
We prefer to call it a stiff upper lip.
好了 够了
Okay, okay. Enough.
米克 为什么叫我们来
Mick, what's the deal with the bat signal?
威斯康辛州发生了一起事故
There was an incident in Wisconsin.
被列为「动物袭击」
"Animal attack."
一个女孩 海登·福斯特进了医院
A girl named Hayden Foster's in the hospital,
她哥哥 被掏了心脏
and her brother lost his heart.
似乎是狼人
Looks like a werewolf.
他们一般不留活口的
Well, they don't usually leave behind survivors.
可能还没干完就被吓跑了
Freak probably got spooked before it could finish the job.
或许吧
Well, perhaps.
但一般的狼人不会被
But it usually takes more than a fright.
吓一下就不吃晚餐了
to put your average werewolf off his supper.
- 这你有了解 是吗 - 还真是
- You'd know that, would you? - Actually, I would.
我在肯德里克斯对狼人进行过深入研究
I did extensive research into lycanthropy at Kendricks.
肯德里克斯
Kendricks?
肯德里克斯学校
The Kendricks School.
是英国记录者训练特工的地方
It's where the British Men of Letters train their operatives.
- 就像我们的 - 霍格沃茨吗
- It's like our - Hogwarts?
是啊
Exactly.
肯德里克斯有全球最大的神秘传说收藏
Kendricks is the largest collection of occult lore in the world.
厉害
Cool.
对于狼人 我了解不少
So when it comes to werewolves, I'm not entirely ignorant.
比如 我们知道昨晚的袭击
For example, we know that last night's attack.
并不是发生在月圆时
didn't happen on a full moon.
因此 这是个纯血狼人
Therefore, we're looking for a pureblood.
还用说
You think?
看起来很轻松
It's like a milk run to me.
那你不介意我跟去喽
Then you don't mind if I tag along?
米克
Mick…
那个 我觉得
Listen, I-I don't think…
你不会擅长这种事的
I don't think it's really your kind of thing.
那或许我该擅长
No, maybe it should be.
我本来有最棒的团队
I had the best team,
但我们大多数人 只是研究者 不是战士
but most of us, we were thinkers, not fighters.
我们说实话 你们和你们妈妈
And let's be honest … your and your mum,
你们是我还活着的唯一原因
you're the only reason I'm still alive.
- 那么你想成为我们这样吗 - 不是
- So now you wanna be like us? - No.
我只是想为接下来的任何情况做好准备
I just want to be ready for whatever's next.
哥们 他就是累赘 你也清楚
Dude, he is dead weight, and you know it.
听着 米克的确是没经验
Look, Mick's inexperienced, sure.
但他们的知识储备很丰富
But these people have some serious knowledge.
那又如何 我们的工作是没法从书本上学到的
So? Dude, what we do, you can't learn this crap in a book.
穿上件法兰绒 拿把枪 然后出去
You put on a flannel, you pick up a gun, you go out there.
要么快速上手 要么早进坟墓
Either you get good fast or you get dead faster.
我们现在跟他们合作了
We're working with these people now.
而且我们成果不错 我们在救人
and … and we're getting wins. We're saving people.
他们能力越强 我们也越好
The better they are, the better we are.
听着 米克在始祖面前也临危不乱
Look, Mick held his own with the Alpha.
为什么不给他个机会 或许他能帮上忙
Why not give him a shot? Maybe he'll come in handy.
如果他害死了自己呢
And what if he gets himself killed?
- 我听到了 - 很好
- I heard that. - Good.
如果他要来 你负责看着他
If he's coming, you're babysitting him.
在路德的第27部论文中
In Luther's 27th thesis,
「打油诗」一词显然是
the word "jingle" is an obvious nod.
指一位15世纪的聪明僧人
to a canny 15th century monk…
你还非得让他听播客吗
Had to let him listen to his podcast, huh?
哥们 这很有教育意义
Dude, it's educational.
再说 我早就想听这个了
And besides, I've been wanting to listen to this one.
马丁·路德这样的僧侣
You know, monks like Martin Luther.
是最早的猎人之一
are among the earliest Hunters.
你拿的书有一部分也是他写的
He even wrote parts of that book you're holding.
什么 这传说能追溯到16世纪
What? This lore dates back to the 16th century?
- 是的 欧洲什么东西都很老 - 嗯
- Yeah. Well, in Europe, everything's old. - Well…
但我们在对付狼人方面
Though we do have our fair share of new tricks.
也有些新诀窍 硫酸盐毒气
for dealing with wolves … sulfate gas,
硝酸银致死注射剂
silver nitrate lethal injection.
一把银色子弹比那些高档玩意都强
Take a handful of silver bullets over any of that fancy crap.
是啊 由于这些「高档玩意」
Yes, well, thanks to that "fancy crap, "
英国最后一次狼人爆发是20年代了
Britain's last werewolf outbreak was in the '20s.
我们把他们肃清了 不管是被咬还是纯血的
We rooted them out, bitten and pureblood alike.
等等 都杀了
Wait a second. You killed them all?
连那些没伤人的也是吗
Even the ones that weren't hurting anyone?
- 什么 - 狼人跟大部分怪物不同
- Sorry? - I mean, werewolves aren't like most monsters.
有些人能控制好 我们有个好朋友被咬了
Some can control it. I mean, we … we have a buddy got bit.
他一直在吃牛心
Nothing but beef hearts ever since.
你们信任他
And you trust him?
杀戮是狼人的基本需求
Well, killing is a fundamental need for werewolves.
怪物不会改变本性
And monsters don't just stop being monsters.
盖思做到了
Well, Garth did.
这里转弯
Turn here.
（野鹿旅馆）
这里似乎有点…
This place, uh, seems a little…
简陋了 是啊
Shabby? Yeah.
我只能搞到三星级的了
Three stars was the best I could do.
至少我们的账房该高兴了
Least our bean counters will be happy.
我给大家订了套间
Booked us all suites.
等等 我们分房住吗
Wait, you… We're in separate rooms?
当然了
Yeah, of course.
三星吗
You say three stars?
是啊
Yeah.
干净毛巾 小瓶洗发水吗
So we're talking fresh towels, little baby shampoos?
好像还有个泳池
And I believe there's a pool.
- 欢迎 先生 - 谢谢
- Welcome, sir. - Cheers, mate.
拿包
Get the bags.
谢谢
Thanks.
天呐 那枕头啊 是吧
Man. Those pillows, right?
还有上面放的小巧克力
The little chocolates that they put on?
我腐化了 萨姆
I mean, I'm ruined, Sam.
这些英国佬是把我带坏了
Those limey sons of bitches ruined me.
我今早还去游泳了
I even took a swim this morning.
你带泳衣了
You brought a swimsuit?
没有
No.
- 你都干什么了 - 我又读了好多米克的传说书
- What'd you get up to? - I read through more of Mick's lore books.
不是吧 这三星在你身上是浪费了
Really? Wow. Those three stars are wasted on you.
总之 听着 这简直不可思议
Anyways, listen to this. It's crazy.
看来30年代时 他们研究了
So apparently, back in the '30s, they were working on.
针对狼人的治疗方案
this treatment for werewolves.
血液疗法
This, like, blood therapy.
是血浆疗法
Plasma therapy.
恐怕并没用处
Useless, I'm afraid.
你们住得如何 各位
So how were your accommodations, lads?
我在宝贝里睡得更香过
I've had better nights sleep in my baby.
上车 我们走
Get in. Let's go.
才不要让他得意呢
Not gonna give him the satisfaction.
等等 我们来吧
Wait, wait. Let us.
跟悲痛中的亲人谈话 比你想的要难
Talking to a grieving family, it's tougher than you think.
- 我学得快 - 那敢情好
- I'm a quick study. - Well, good for you.
待在这儿 望风
Okay, stay here, keep watch.
如果有情况就…吹哨吧
Anything comes up… I don't know, whistle.
福斯特女士
Ms. Foster?
抱歉打搅 麦克维探员
Sorry to bother you. Agent McVie.
这位是我搭档 弗利特伍德探员
This is my partner, Agent Fleetwood.
我们想问你女儿几个问题
We'd like to ask your daughter a few questions.
她在睡觉
She's sleeping.
我们很快就完的
We'll be quick. Promise.
不行
I said no.
海登需要休息 她…
Hayden needs her rest. She's…
早上好 病人今天如何
Good morning. And how is our patient today?
抱歉 你是谁
I'm sorry. Who are you?
白金汉医生 海登的主治医生 马克姆医生
Dr. Buckingham. Hayden's attending doctor, Dr. Markum,
让我来看看她的
asked me to look in on her.
能麻烦几位
Would it be okay.
出去一下吗
to ask you just to step outside for a moment?
我…当然 医生
I, um…Of course, Doctor.
- 好 - 谢谢
- Sure. - Thank you.
- 来 别客气 - 谢谢
- Here. Please. - Thank you.
没事
No problem.
刚刚抱歉
I'm sorry, about all that.
没事的
Please.
你遭遇了这样的事 没有理由道歉的
After what you've been through, you have no reason to apologize.
我妈妈在哪
Where's my mom?
你妈妈就在外面
Your mum's just outside.
我就给你看看 确保你没事
Just gonna take a quick look, make sure you're okay.
真勇敢
Brave girl.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
那一切好快
It was so fast.
你受了惊吓
You've had quite a shock.
我都不知道孩子们为什么会去那儿
I just … I don't even know what my kids were doing out there.
海登本该是去朋友家
You know, Hayden was supposed to be sleeping.
过夜了 本…
at her friend's house, and … and Ben…
我一直在想这是个噩梦
I just keep thinking this is a nightmare, you know?
我会醒来
That I'm gonna wake up.
好吧
Okay.
幸好联调局来了
I'm just glad the FBI is here,
不是那些疯子
not those crazies.
- 疯子 - 找大脚怪的
- Crazies? - Bigfoot truthers.
又是打电话 又是发邮件
Calling, sending e-mails.
他们以为海登…
They thought Hayden was…
我说了 疯子
Like I said. Crazy.
还有个姑娘来过
Some girl even came by here.
说是鱼类及野生动物管理局的
saying she was from the Fish and Wildlife Service.
跟海登也就差不多大
Barely as old as Hayden.
我信了才怪呢
I mean, like I'm gonna buy that.
记得她什么样吗
You remember what she looked like?
嗯 金发 态度很差
Yeah. Blonde. Bad attitude.
我还有她的名片
I actually … I have her card right here.
很好
Good.
糟糕
No.
好吧
Okay.
你没事
You're okay.
放松 好吗
You relax, okay?
她…
Is she…
伤口愈合得很好
Wound's healing up nicely.
不太严重
Nothing too serious.
- 那…谢谢你 - 不客气
- That's so … Thank you so much. - Pleasure.
失陪
Excuse me.
医生
Doc?
怎么样
So?
海登被咬了吗
Was Hayden bit?
没有 她很幸运
No. No, she's a lucky girl.
那就好 鱼类及野生动物管理局那个呢
Good. What about, uh, Fish and Wildlife Service?
- 会不会也是个猎人 - 年轻 金发 火大
- Think it's another hunter? - Young, blonde, pissed off.
耳熟吗
Sound like anybody we know?
（加油站）
（乔迪 旅行如何 威斯康辛大学还好吗）
校园不错
"Campus is nice."
喂 我是碧翠丝·奎比探员
Hello? Uh, this is Agent Beatrice Quimby.
太好了 有只熊
Oh, thank God. There's a bear.
简直有坦克大小
It's the size of a freakin' tank!
它好像是冲着我的野餐篮子来的
I think it wants my pic-a-nic basket!
你好 迪恩
Hi, Dean.
鱼类及野生动物管理局 不是吧
So Fish and Wildlife? Really?
克莱尔 你来这儿做什么
Claire, what are you doing here?
跟你们一样 查狼人的案子
Same as you. Werewolf case.
好了 大家喝啤酒吧
Now. Beers all around.
- 你是谁 - 米克·戴维斯
- Who are you? - Oh. Mick Davies.
英国记录者
Men of Letters. British.
说来话长 像《唐顿庄园》那么无聊
Long story. And, like, "Downton Abbey" boring, so…
不行
No.
好吧 总之
Okay. Anyway…
我已经查了一天了 猜怎么着
I've been on this a day. And guess what?
那个姑娘 海登
The girl, Hayden?
她关于袭击当晚的说法
Her story about what happened the night of the attack?
根本是撒谎
One big lie.
- 她妈妈也这么说 - 她去哪了
- Her mom said the same thing. - Where was she?
她去当地小酒吧 喝酒了
She was at the local dive bar, gettin' trashed.
我追踪了她的手机 还打听了一下
I tracked her phone and asked around and…
酒保都喜欢我 这是天赋
Bartenders love me. It's a gift.
好吧 你还查到什么吗
Right. You get anything else?
跟我说话的那人是个人渣
The guy I talked to was a scumbag.
帮派文身 骑机车 动手动脚
Tribal tat, motorcycle, grabby.
动手动脚
Grabby?
我是个大姑娘了 我应付他了
I'm a big girl. I handled it.
好吧 今晚我就到这儿了
Right. Think I'm gonna call it a night.
哥们 这才5：30
D-dude, it's 5:30.
嗯 但我6点整要做报告
Yeah, but my report's due at 6:00 sharp.
只工作 不玩耍
All work, no play.
认识你很高兴
Nice meeting ya.
你们的外国交换生好逊
So your foreign exchange student is totally lame.
是啊 他跟萨姆可好了
Yeah. He's Sam's best friend.
就像书呆子灵魂伴侣
They're like nerd soul mates.
总之 你为什么一个人
Anyway, why are you alone?
乔迪忙着警长事宜
Jody's busy with sheriff stuff.
她说如果有发现就给她打电话
And she said to call if I found anything.
你打给她了
So you called her?
你们先打来了
You called first.
而且她很好的 艾莉克斯也是
And she's great, by the way. And so is Alex.
我们该去停尸房吗
So should we go to the morgue?
慢着点 克莱尔 停尸房关门了
Take it easy, Clarice. Morgue's closed.
对了 你上次吃热餐是什么时候了
By the way, when's the last time you had a hot meal.
加油站微波炉饭不算
that didn't come from a-a Gas-n-Sip microwave?
这也没什么不好
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
挺久了
It's been a while.
那么…
Well…
随便点 哈利·波特付钱
Go nuts. It's on, uh, Harry Potter.
好啊
Cool.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不
No!
谢谢你们这么快赶来
Thanks for coming by so quickly.
福斯特女士给了我们你们的电话
Ms. Foster gave us your number.
知道她是怎么回事吗
You have any idea what happened to her?
明天尸检
Autopsy's tomorrow,
但可能是动脉栓塞
but it could be an arterial embolism,
- 心脏骤停 - 她这年纪心脏病
- cardiac arrest. - A heart attack at her age?
还有更怪的
It gets weirder.
她入院时 手臂上有防御伤
When we admitted her, she had defensive wounds to her arms.
现在呢
Now…
都消失了
they're gone.
给我点时间
Just, uh, give me a second.
好
Sure.
好吧 怎么回事
Okay…what the hell?
你检查过海登 注意到奇怪之处了吗
You checked Hayden out. Did you notice anything weird?
没有 但她可能有内伤
No, but, uh, the girl could've had internal injuries or…
但她的外伤都愈合了 不可能
But somehow, her external injuries all healed? No way.
这就像是
This is almost like, uh…
或许她转化了
You know, what if she turned?
「变狼」吗
What, like, "wolfed out" turned?
那狼人愈合的事就能解释了
Explains the whole Wolverine healing factor thing.
嗯 那不可能
Yeah, no, but that'd be crazy.
因为那样的话 她就该是被咬了
because that means she would've been bit.
而米克说她没被咬
And Mick here says that that didn't happen.
是吧 米克
Right, Mick?
是啊 我没看到
No, not … not that I saw.
你百分百确定吗
Are you 100%?
或许我错了
Unless I made a mistake.
- 好个错误 - 迪恩
- Hell of a mistake. - Dean…
不 我就说不该带上他
No, I told you we shouldn't have dragged him along.
- 我说过的 - 行了
- I told you! - Don't!
伤了海登的东西还在
Whatever got Hayden is still out there.
好吧
Okay.
那么袭击当晚
So let's say the night of the attack,
狼人杀了哥哥 然后咬了妹妹
wolf ices big bro, chomps down on a little sis,
然后就消失了 这合理吗
and then…poof, vanishes? Does that make any sense?
或许他放了她
Maybe he let her go.
有意的 为什么
On purpose? Why?
或许他不希望她死 而是希望她转化
Perhaps he didn't want her dead. He wanted her turned.
是啊 那么这就不是随机的
Right. Which means this wasn't random.
那就是认识她的人干的
Which means it would've been somebody who knew her.
- 朋友 亲人 - 或是酒吧的人
- Friends, family. - Or someone from the bar.
好吧 萨姆 你和克莱尔
Okay. All right, Sam, you and Claire,
去找她本该去那家待的女孩谈话
you go talk to the girl that she was supposed to be crashing with,
我和门外汉去酒吧 看能查到什么
and me and amateur hour will hit the bar, see what shakes loose.
说真的 情况都挺好
So… really? Things are good?
嗯 可好了
Yeah. They're awesome.
真的吗 确定
Really? You sure?
哥们 相信我吧
Dude, take the yes.
好了
Okay.
- 你在这里等着 - 什么
- So you wait here. - What?
萨姆 别见怪
Sam, no offense,
但你觉得孩子会愿意跟谁说话
but who do you think the kids are gonna wanna talk to?
我 还是个老头子
Me, or some old skeezer?
是啊
Exactly.
就回来
Be right back.
老头子
Skeezer?
（林肯地区高中）
迪恩 医院的事
Dean, what happened back there…
我的错
my mistake,
- 不会有下次了 - 那最好
- it won't happen again. - Better not.
怎么了
Problem?
腕管综合征
The old carpal tunnel.
我来吧 大人
Well, allow me, your lordship.
谢谢
Thanks.
好啊
Howdy.
斯特拉姆探员 他是瓦尔探员
Agent Strummer. This is Agent Vai.
认得这姑娘吗
Do you recognize this girl?
她三晚前来过
She was here three nights ago.
嗯 不认识
Yeah. Not really.
我要是卖酒给未成年女孩也会撒谎
Yeah, I'd lie if I served underage girls, too.
听着 伙计
Look, man, I…
我真的很需要这份工作
I really need this job. I…
她几周前开始来的
She started coming in a few weeks ago.
是在康纳受雇后
after Conner got hired.
康纳
Conner?
另一个酒保 他们有点意思
Yeah, the other bartender. They're having a thing.
什么样的意思
What kind of a thing?
自己问吧
Ask him.
康纳
Hi, Conner.
文身不错
Nice ink.
喜欢高中女生 是吗
So you like high school girls, do you?
你越来越老 品味却还是同一个年纪 是吗
You get older, they stay the same age. Is that it?
不是这样的
That's not how it was.
那么你没有在跟海登·福斯特约会
So you weren't dating Hayden Foster?
约会 不 我偶尔放她进来
Dating? No, I let her in from time to time.
她性感到爆 好吗
She is stupid hot. Okay?
- 但仅此而已 我发誓 - 她遇袭那晚
- But that's it. I swear. - And the night she got attacked,
你那晚也让她进来了吗
did you let her in that night, too?
听着 我不知道发生了什么
Look, I don't know what happened.
我那晚一直在酒吧后面
I was behind the bar the whole night.
我都没看到她离开
I didn't even see her leave.
然后呢
And then what'd you do?
回家了吧
Guess I went home.
了吧
You guess?
这问题很简单 康纳
Well, it's a simple question, Conner.
我问你做了什么 你告诉我
I ask what you were doing, then you tell me.
比如 你昨晚做了什么
For instance, what were you doing last night?
- 我吗 - 嗯
- Me? - ‭Yeah.
我写报告来着
I was writing my report.
然后呢
And then? ‭
我看了一集《英国烘焙大赛》
Well, I watched an episode of "The Great British Bake Off"
- 然后就睡了 - 看到了吧
- and went to bed. - See?
多简单
Simple.
我回家了
I went home, man.
我没把那姑娘怎么样
And I didn't do anything to that girl, okay?
嗯 再看看吧
Yeah. Well, we'll see.
还有件事
One more thing. Um…
你前两天晚上
Did you happen to meet a.
有没有见过一个金发姑娘
blonde girl the other night?
大概这么高 脾气挺大
About yay high. Feisty?
嗯 她说自己是海登的亲戚
Yeah, yeah. Said she was Hayden's cousin.
那疯婆子还冲我丢啤酒
Crazy bitch threw a beer at me.
据我所知 你活该
Well, from what I heard, you earned it.
怎么 你是她爸吗
What are you, her dad?
拜托 那样的姑娘
Dude, come on. Girls like that?
是啊
Yeah.
你再敢碰她 我打烂你的脸
You ever touch her again, I'll break your face.
你干得不错
Nice work in there.
- 谢谢 - 你的不在场证明 我差点信了
- Thank you. - ‭Yeah, that alibi … I almost bought it.
- 什么 - 16岁的姑娘
- Sorry? - ‭See, here's the thing about 16-year-old girls,
尤其是16岁新变成了狼人的姑娘
especially 16-year-old freshly minted werewolf girls …
她们不会平白死去
they don't just die.
你一整天都奇奇怪怪的
And you've been acting sketchy all day.
我不知道你说什么呢
I don't know what you're talking about.
你把她怎么了
What did you do to her?
我做了该做的
I did what needed to be done.
- 什么意思 - 昨晚
- And that means? - Last night,
我给她注射了硝酸银
I injected her with silver nitrate.
- 你杀了她 - 她袭击了我
- So you killed her? - Well, she attacked me.
她撕裂了我的肩膀 而且…
She tore up my shoulder. And…
- 我有命在身 - 你有选择
- I had orders. - ‭You had a choice.
是吗
Did I?
我们的工作就是杀怪物
Killing monsters is what we do.
或许你老跟恶魔和女巫交好
Or maybe palling around with demons and witches,
- 都忘记这点了 - 少教我怎么做工作
- you've forgotten. - Don't tell me how to do my job.
- 那你做好啊 - 你觉得就那么简单
- Well, then do it. - You think it's that simple, huh?
- 是的 - 是吗
- I really do. ‭- Yeah?
我以前也那么想
I used to think the same thing.
告诉你
Well, here's a little tip.
真实世界不是非黑即白的
Things aren't just black and white out here.
你面前的只是个案子 比如海登
All you have is a case in front of you, like Hayden.
几个月前 有个孩子 一个灵力者
A few months ago, there was this kid, this psychic.
她杀了人 但她不是有意的
She was killing people, but she didn't mean to hurt anyone.
她遭到了虐待
She was being abused.
所以我们给了她个机会
So we gave her a second chance.
因为那是正确的做法
because it was the right thing to do.
那是你的特权
Well… that's your luxury.
我们有准则
We have a code.
谢谢 凯奇先生
Thank you, Mr. Ketch.
现在海登的妈妈
Well, now Hayden's mom,
她要下葬两个孩子 而不是一个了
she gets to bury two kids instead of one,
就因为你 和你的准则
thanks to you and thanks to your code.
干得好
Nice work.
我之前是开玩笑
I was kidding before,
但你看上去真的像变态
but you really do look like a creeper.
好笑 怎么样了
Funny. How'd it go?
闺蜜找到了 秘密告诉我了
BFF found. Beans spilled.
海登在偷偷跟一个年长的人约会
Hayden was hooking up with this older guy on the DL,
她很喜欢他 但他很粘人
and she was really into him, but he was a total stalker.
时时刻刻地发短信 超级有占有欲
Texting constantly, ultra possessive.
她朋友觉得受不了 对海登哥哥告密了
Skeeved her friend out so much she narc'd to Hayden's brother.
那就怪不得他会在了
Guess that explains why he was there.
我做得不错吧
I did good, right?
克莱尔 乔迪为什么认为
Claire, why does Jody think.
你去了麦迪逊看大学
you're in Madison looking at colleges?
你打给了她
You called her?
你说了吗
Did you tell?
还没有 但你为什么要对她撒谎
No. Not yet. But why are you lying to her?
我知道 好吗
Look, I-I know, okay?
我知道我非常亏欠乔迪
I know how much I owe Jody.
但我们试过猎魔
But we tried the whole hunting thing, and…
结果都是我坐在车上
I just ended up sitting in the car.
她包揽一切
while she does everything.
那她是想慢慢来
Guess she's taking it slow.
她是希望我正常一点
She wants me to be normal,
像艾莉克斯那样上护士学校
go to nursing school like Alex.
- 她真那么说了吗 - 她不用说出来
- Did she actually say that? - She doesn't have to.
我自己混更好
I'm better off on my own.
这样 大家都开心
This way, everybody's happy.
克莱尔 乔迪发现后不会开心的
Claire, Jody's not gonna be happy when she finds out.
如果你出了事
And if something happened to you…
我很小心的
I'm careful!
你得告诉她实情
You need to tell her the truth.
知道吗
You know what?
去你的
Screw you.
我烦透了你们插手我的生活
I'm so sick of you guys dive-bombing my life,
- 假装在乎我 - 我们是在乎
- pretending like you care. - We do care.
那就别把我当做傻孩子
Then stop treating me like a stupid kid!
那你自己别犯傻
Then stop acting like one.
克莱尔
Claire…
天呐
Oh, my…
克莱尔 是我 是我
Claire. Hey, it's me. It's me.
是我 有我呢 你没事了
It's me. I gotcha. I gotcha. I gotcha. You're safe.
我们得给她降温 她在发烧
We gotta cool her off. She's burning up.
不不 保持她的体温
No. No, no, keep her warm.
- 别管 - 闭嘴
- Back off. - ‭Shut up.
听着 我理解你们生我气
Look, I understand you're angry …
米克 你杀了个孩子
Mick, you killed a kid.
我们不是生气 我们跟你完了
We're not angry. We're done!
我还有多久就会…
How long have I got until…
有时候要到满月 有时候只要一段时间
Sometimes it takes a full moon. Sometimes it just takes time.
听我说
Hey, listen to me.
听着 没人说这会轻松
Look, nobody said this was gonna be easy, okay?
- 但你可以继续生活 - 不可能
- But you can live with this. - No way.
听着 是啊 一个月你有几晚
Look, so you … you have to stay locked up.
得被关起来 好吗
a few nights out of the month, okay?
其他时间 你还是你
The rest of the time, you're you.
除非我闯出来
Unless I break out.
或许有些人能控制得了
Maybe some people can control this,
但我平时都难以控制好自己
but I can barely keep it together on a good day.
如果我
So if there's any.
有可能会伤到乔迪或艾莉克斯
chance I could hurt Jody or Alex…
或是任何人
or anyone…
那我宁可死
I'd rather die.
克莱尔 或许还有别的办法
Claire, there may be another way.
还有你之前提到的血液疗法
There's … there's the blood therapy that you talk about.
我说了 根本没用
I told you, it doesn't work.
这里说
It says right here, uh,
九个实验对象中有一人被治愈
1 out of 9 test subjects was cured.
- 治愈了 - 对
- Cured? - ‭Yes.
那是用老鼠做的研究
That study was on mice.
告诉我他在说什么
You want to tell me what the hell he's talking about?
我们用长狼人的血做过实验
We experimented with the blood of sire werewolves.
结果发现无法逆转
And we found it was possible to reverse.
啮齿类动物早期的狼人转化
the early stages of lycanthropy…in rodents.
你们没拿人类实验过
So you never tested on humans?
- 就一次 - 怎么样
- Once. - ‭And?
那人痛苦死去了
The subject died in agony.
对不起
Sorry.
或许第二次就能成功
Maybe second time's a charm.
不不 你没有发言权
No, no. You don't get a vote in this.
这是我的人生
It's my life.
我有绝对权利
I get all the votes.
萨姆 你要支持我一下吗
Sam, you wanna back me up here?
是她的人生
It's her life.
你觉得这是个好方案吧
I bet you think this is a great solution.
要么成功 要么她死掉
It works, or she dies.
不管怎样 都少了一个怪物 是吧
Either way, one less monster, right?
我不觉得有任何好方案
I don't think there's any great solutions here.
迪恩
Dean…
求你 我不能这么活
Please? I can't.
好吧
All right.
如果我们这么做
If we do this … if…
我们要怎么做
how do we get it done?
我们需要血 活血
We need blood, live blood,
来自咬她的狼人的
from the werewolf that bit her.
好 那是谁
Good. Great. Who we lookin' at?
帮派文身 酒吧那个
Tribal tat. Back at the bar.
我们警告他别碰克莱尔 她马上就挨咬了
We shook him down about Claire, and right after, she gets bit.
这不是巧合
That's not a coincidence.
时间线符合 与两名受害人都有联系
Timeline fits, connection to both victims.
那我们去吧
Then we should go.
不到一小时就是满月了
The full moon rises in less than an hour.
如果她转化进食
And if she turns and feeds,
成功率就降至零了
our cheery success rate drops to zero.
走吧
Let's go.
你别去
Not you.
你留下陪她
You stay with her.
- 你信任他 - 米克很聪明
- You trust him? - Mick's a smart guy.
所以他知道 如果她发生任何事
So when I say that if anything happens to her,
- 任何事 - 你会杀了我
- and I mean anything… - You'll kill me.
就像我说的 聪明
Like I said, smart.
萨姆 如果你不回来
Sam, if you're not back…
我们会回来的
We'll be back.
（麦芽酒）
（幸运獾酒吧）
好了 别动 是银的
All right, don't move, don't move. It's silver.
他是人
He's human.
等一等
Let's give it time.
好疼
It burns!
你不懂 已经开始了
You don't understand. It's happening!
- 给我 - 不行
- Give it to me! - ‭No.
那你动手 快点 开始了
Then you do it, please! It's happening!
你不懂这是什么感觉
And you don't understand how this feels!
我知道有个人 现在就会打死你
I know a man who would shoot you right now.
毫不犹豫
without a moment's thought.
我的每个直觉都说 他是对的
And every instinct I have says he's right…
我也该尽责
that I ought to do my duty.
但是
‭But…
但我的直觉最近不是很好
But my instincts haven't been so grand of late.
坐下
Sit down.
好了 我们这么办
Now okay, here's what we're gonna do.
首先 我们把你绑上
Firstly, we're gonna restrain you, right?
好保护我
For my protection. Okay?
然后
And then…
给你打镇定剂
then we're gonna sedate you.
也是为了保护我
Also for my protection.
如果幸运 等你醒来 一切就都结束了
With any luck, when you wake up, this will all be over.
如果我醒得来
If I wake up.
我得打给乔迪
I gotta call Jody.
她会气死的
She's gonna be so mad at me.
克莱尔 退后
Claire, get back!
克莱尔
Claire?
她在哪
Where is she?
那狼人 带走了她
The wolf, he took her.
我怎么说的
What did I tell you?!
我想阻止他的 好吗
I tried to stop him, okay?
我能找到她
I can find her.
我在她兜里放了个追踪器
I put a tracker in her pocket.
你给她放了追踪器
You planted a bug on her?
你回头再杀我 我们先找到克莱尔
Look, you can kill me later, after we find Claire.
我知道这挺突然
I know this is sudden,
但你和你的朋友 本该让我得到海登的
but you and your friends, you should've let me have Hayden.
她在这里那么痛苦
She was miserable here. She…
我们有宏大的计划
We had big plans.
是吗 那是你咬她之前还是之后
Yeah? Was that before or after you bit her?
我需要知道她能不能在转化中活下来
I had to know if she could survive the change.
不是每个人都行
Not everyone does.
瞧
See?
起初很疼 但最终
It hurts at first, but eventually,
这感觉就像最好的毒品再乘一千
it's like the best drug ever times a thousand.
去你的吧 少狼
Right. Eat me, Teen Wolf.
我也不想这样
It's not like I want to do this.
我的族群 本来过得很好 我们不伤人
My pack, we were happy. We didn't hurt anyone.
然后拿着我前所未见的武器的猎人
And then hunters with weapons that I've never seen before,
跑来了
they show up and…
轻松干掉了我们20个人
…take out 20 of us, just like that.
剩下的我们分头跑了
The ones that made it, we split up,
但我们不该这么活的
but we weren't meant to live like that.
狼人需要族群
A werewolf needs his pack.
你会发现的 我是个好人
You'll see, I'm a nice guy.
是吗 知道都谁说自己是好人吗
Yeah? You know who says they're a nice guy?
有恋母情结的粘人没安全感的小贱婊
Clingy, insecure bitches with mommy issues.
你这么说只是因为转化过程
That's just the change talking.
你吃过感觉会好得多
You'll feel better once you eat.
试试吧 你会喜欢的
Try it. You'll like it.
我一看见你 就知道
As soon as I saw you, I knew…
你跟我一样
you're just like me.
孤独
Alone.
错了
Wrong.
我有家人 他们爱我
I have a family, and they love me.
克莱尔
‭Claire?
Claire. ‭
好了 放松
Hey, all right. Easy.
米克 快
Mick, hurry!
对不起 孩子
Sorry, kid.
闪开
Move, move, move, move, move.
克莱尔 克莱尔
Claire. Claire.
克莱尔 是我们 你认识我们的
Okay, Claire, it's us. You know us.
- 那玩意好了吗 - 好了 去吧
- That thing ready yet? - It's ready. It's ready. Go, go, go.
- 这是她的愿望 是吗 - 是的
- She wanted this, right? - Oh, yeah.
我去喘口气
Gonna get some air.
克莱尔
Claire?
迪恩
Dean.
你们脸色好差
You guys look like crap.
好了 这个给你
All right, give this to you.
那姑娘是个奇迹
That girl is a walking miracle.
是啊
Yes, she is.
听着
Listen,
- 谢谢你帮我们 - 嗯
- thanks for the win back there. - Yeah.
- 那我们没事了吧 - 还不算
- So we're good? - Not quite,
但我们可以再给你个机会
but we'll give you a second chance.
别搞砸了 不会再有一次了
Just don't mess it up. There won't be a third.
好
Okay.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
老实说
Honestly?
我现在有点想吃骨头饼干
I'm sort of craving a Milk-Bone right now.
听着
Look, um…
我之前说的话
what I said before…
我需要时你们都在
you guys are here when I need you.
这才是最重要的
and that's all that matters.
你要告诉乔迪发生了什么吗
You gonna tell Jody what happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
不管你决定怎样 我们会帮你
Well, whatever you decide, we got your back.
嘟声后请留言
Leave a message after the tone.
是我 克莱尔
It's me, Claire.
好吧 我说了
Okay, um, here it goes.
我一直在一个人猎魔
I've been hunting. Alone.
我知道这你不想听到
And I know it's not what you want to hear.
我知道这听上去很可怕
And I know it sounds scary.
我有时候也害怕
It scares me, too, sometimes, but…
但这件事我必须自己做
this is something I have to do on my own.
就这一阵的
Just for a little while.
但我准备好了
But I'm ready,
如果没有你
and I never would've been.
做我妈妈 我不可能准备好
if it wasn't for you being my mother.
我该挂了
Well, I better go.
叫艾莉克斯别动我的东西
Tell Alex she better not touch my stuff.
我爱你们
I love you guys.